1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
AHHHHHH
Which one did you lose?
HAHAHAHAHA
You're a cat!
I'm a cat!
Excuse me
Yes?
Um, can I get an autograph on my
favorite hair?
Yes!
Excuse me
What color do you like?
Um...
I really like Haru-chan's hair, so I'll
go with pink
Ah, pink!
Thank you
Are you a fan of her?
Ah, thank you!
Thank you
Ah, wait!
Um, can you say it with a lot of love?
Ah, I understand!
With a lot of love
Eh?
Do I have to say it with a lot of love?
You do!
Ah, wait!
More!
Ah, that's not enough!
I have to say it with a lot of love
That's not true!
You two, don't fight for me!
I got it
Ah, you're in trouble!
This is a problem
You're in trouble!
I can't believe it
This is a problem
Thank you very much!
So cute!
I'll come again!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Where should I write this?
Okay
Like a high school student
Thank you very much!
Hironi's room
Which one is it?
Hello
Hi
This is Hironi's room
What are you doing today?
Today is
What day is it today?
Why?
It's not.
It's 13 o'clock, so we are having a
talk session on the day of the coming-
of-age ceremony.
What are we talking about?
It's about the 2016's.
It's almost 16 years old.
I'm 16 years old.
No way.
When this video is broadcast, I'll be
16 years old.
I'm 16 years old.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I got a cake from a fan.
Was it good?
Yes, it was.
I ate a lot of strawberries.
I'm 16 years old.
You are still 16 years old.
I'm 18 years old.
I'm 16 years old.
You are young.
I'm sure you'll be happy when you see
me.
I'm sure you'll be happy.
Will you say that?
Thank you.
This program is a program in which six
people who are active to promote
something exciting challenge various
things and raise the barometer of
excitement in the world.
I'm still biting my teeth.
That's right, recklessly.
We are going to have a special event
today!
Oh!
Hello!
I'm Hitoka!
I'm Oharu!
We are going to have a special event
today!
Let's wait for cute Haachan!
No!
Wait!
We are going to have a special event in
a year.
Yes, in a year.
I'm going to have a special event in
two years.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, in two years.
Kanamin Seijin is...
Kanamin Seijin?
Kanamin Seijin, Kanamin Seijin, Kanamin
Seijin!
It's already open.
It's open.
It's a farewell.
I'm alone. What should I do?
Shiori-chan?
Yes?
It's open.
Yeah!
Bye bye!
Photo!
It's real!
I thought it was fake.
Wow, it smells!
Wow!
Cute!
Big!
How is it?
It's hot!
Ta-da!
How was your New Year's Day?
We have a new program!
Bye-bye!
The winner of rock-paper-scissors will
eat the mandarin.
Let's go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
I lost.
I want it.
If I win the next game, I can eat one.
I'll eat one.
Let's go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
I won.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Cheers!
I heard that this spring, a new single
of my favorite idol, Tokimeki Sendembu,
will be released.
Isn't it great?
It's not the time to eat mandarin
oranges in a place like this.
I have to check it.
I have not done it yet but
Konnichiwa
It's delicious.
It's sour.
Is it sour?
I don't know.
Cheers.
It's warm.
It's strong.
It's so sour.
It's a color.
I'm not sure.
It's warm.
We finished eating.
Cheers.
We met the cameraman.
Well...
I'll eat a tangerine.
You're hungry, aren't you?
I'll drink it.
It smells good.
It's a real tangerine.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Isn't it fun to wear a kotatsu?
Kanamin!
You look a little yellow.
I ate too much mandarin orange.
Kanamin, you ate too much mandarin
orange and became like this.
I think it's a little too much fun, but
you're still cute.
Thank you!
Kanamin!
What's this?
Two-headed Kanamin.
I'm Oragune.
I'm a little necky.
Oh, you're necky.
But you're two-headed.
I'm a little bit of a two-headed
Kanamin.
Come here.
Kagamimochi.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Yeah.
What are you looking at?
What do you see when you look inside?
This smells good.
Yes, it smells good.
This is real.
You can eat it.
Hi, Jojo TV.
What are you doing?
What is this?
This is a certain entertainer.
Really?
I'm going to put it on this guy.
No.
Are your eyes good?
I'm a girl with glasses.
Oh, you're cute.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
I'm a girl with glasses.
Oh, that's good.
How do I look?
You know, this way.
Wait, you're wearing bangs.
It's weird.
Hold this.
My bangs.
It's good.
I'll open a new door.
I'm going home.
Bye bye.
Oh! Bye bye!
Kana-Ami!
Yeah!
Bye bye!
Hello!
I'm changing my clothes for Shape Up!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
There are three people who are in the
music video of Koi no Shape Up!
Yuri-san!
Is that Yuri Yoshikawa?
Yes.
She is so cute!
I wonder what role she is playing.
Is she a person?
Yes.
I'm not sure.
I wonder what role she is playing.
She is a person, right?
I was excited when I took off my
glasses.
Hello.
Excuse me. Are you the one in the music
video of Koi no Shape Up, Karami Tsujino
and Bambi Fujimoto?
No, we are not.
But you look a little different.
You don't have enough excitement.
But you are right.
You are cute.
Oh, no! Bambi, you are not in the
video.
Yes!
This part is so
Pathetic
N
Early
Unpredictable
Are you ready?
Up, Step, Down, Down, Down
Dar-kun, it's me.
Here's Bro- vamos.
nothing
Darling!
Spring
The Abyss
Eh? The venue?
Whoa!
Oh my god...
Hallo
WELCOME TO MAVALDIVIA
MAHVILRENA
air showdown
Marquia!
Seph!
Please subscribe to my channel!